There has never been a time in the history of our Country that the Media was so Fraudulent, Fake, or Corrupt! When… https://t.co/bP2Ywfddfv
The  Amazon Washington Post and @CNN just did a Fake Interview on Pardons for Aids on the Wall, and that I didn’t t… https://t.co/dTHAJ57e1g
A sad day for the Democrats, Kirsten Gillibrand has dropped out of the Presidential Primary. I’m glad they never fo… https://t.co/sUvsnRYbiX
Thank you for the support as we MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN! https://t.co/qKgwRMSgcf
Another totally Fake story in the Amazon Washington Post (lobbyist) which states that if my Aides broke the law to… https://t.co/mHnCxS2Rnn
The Wall is going up very fast despite total Obstruction by Democrats in Congress, and elsewhere!… https://t.co/XIMMALXoZr
....And by the way, I’m the best thing that’s ever happened to Puerto Rico!
Puerto Rico is one of the most corrupt places on earth. Their political system is broken and their politicians are… https://t.co/Cf5sPiHSr9
Our Federal Reserve cannot “mentally” keep up with the competition - other countries. At the G-7 in France, all of… https://t.co/gLVGOhy4gM
....I don’t want to Win for myself, I only want to Win for the people. The New @FoxNews is letting millions of GREA… https://t.co/UANHkvOoRu
....are all in for the Open Border Socialists (or beyond). Fox hires “give Hillary the questions” @donnabrazile, Ju… https://t.co/qtk5A0kfT5
Just watched @FoxNews heavily promoting the Democrats through their DNC Communications Director, spewing out whatev… https://t.co/QbMTNutLpr
Would be very hard for Jeremy Corbyn, the leader of Britain’s Labour Party, to seek a no-confidence vote against Ne… https://t.co/zG5Il2b27p
We are tracking closely tropical storm Dorian as it heads, as usual, to Puerto Rico. FEMA and all others are ready,… https://t.co/a74RTnIY3g
So interesting to read and see all of the free and interesting advice I am getting on China, from people who have t… https://t.co/2fhO3RKIKy
“The infestation of bedbugs at The New York Times office” @OANN  was perhaps brought in by lightweight journalist B… https://t.co/RBIUM6743V
A made up Radical Left Story about Doral bedbugs, but Bret Stephens is loaded up with them! Been calling me wrong f… https://t.co/TPmvUbWZ8z
....Another is a one-time BAD Congressman from Illinois who lost in his second term by a landslide, then failed in… https://t.co/YU81W37NUs
Can you believe it? I’m at 94% approval in the Republican Party, and have Three Stooges running against me. One is… https://t.co/ayI5AJt4Nz
Axios (whatever that is) sat back and said GEEEEE, let’s see, what can we make up today to embarrass the President?… https://t.co/hQmXUH48Ou
They do stories so big on Elizabeth “Pocahontas” Warren’s crowd sizes, adding many more people than are actually th… https://t.co/U2Qlsbb74x
It is amazing that I can be at 51% with Zogby when the Fake &amp; Corrupt News is almost 100% against me. Great job Mr. President!
The G7 in France was so successful, and yet when I came back and read the Corrupt and Fake News, and watched numero… https://t.co/eL9zm5T909
Looking forward to being with Dan Bishop in two weeks, in North Carolina. His opponent believes in Open Borders and… https://t.co/hWpx3png5g
.@JudgeJeanine Pirro is following up her #1 Best Seller with another book that is destined to also be #1 – “Radical… https://t.co/8m6tDRAQy0
The Federal Reserve loves watching our manufacturers struggle with their exports to the benefit of other parts of t… https://t.co/riqJdZoQDC
100% Confirmed! https://t.co/qVsmc9zXk4
Wow! Yet another big storm heading to Puerto Rico. Will it ever end? Congress approved 92 Billion Dollars for Puert… https://t.co/JZcruoPI55
The G-7 was a great success for the USA and all. LameStream Media coverage bore NO relationship to what actually ha… https://t.co/IPKwYRolTl
No bedbugs at Doral. The Radical Left Democrats, upon hearing that the perfectly located (for the next G-7) Doral N… https://t.co/pXEWQZIkpb
Starting to look good for the highly respected Prime Minister of the Italian Republic, Giuseppe Conte. Represented… https://t.co/SAR0IduDCn
I have gotten to know President @jairbolsonaro well in our dealings with Brazil. He is working very hard on the Ama… https://t.co/ARKxTNQkbD
Just returned to Washington from France and the very successful G-7, only to find that the Fake News is still tryin… https://t.co/gZKS1nx9lk
Thank you Mark! https://t.co/doRfNAx2Ez
I agree 100%! https://t.co/qteDIrgG9S
THANK YOU FRANCE🇺🇸🇫🇷
#G7Biarritz https://t.co/AHaCT7d5eY
https://t.co/bUjFDj2Kcm
Just wrapped up a great meeting with my friend Prime Minister @NarendraModi of India at the #G7Summit in Biarritz,… https://t.co/kDiJJK6632
Very productive meeting with Angela Merkel, the Chancellor of the Federal Republic of Germany, at the #G7Summit in… https://t.co/xJVmJoCM8A
Great respect for the fact that President Xi &amp; his Representatives want “calm resolution.” So impressed that they a… https://t.co/omV7rMfrkO
The story by Axios that President Trump wanted to blow up large hurricanes with nuclear weapons prior to reaching s… https://t.co/HzEAczrvf3
Great meeting this morning with President @AlsisiOfficial of Egypt at the Hôtel du Palais in Biarritz, France!… https://t.co/zurZ5pDdZ4
https://t.co/9I9DEJ4cD1
All Trump Haters and Lovers must watch. Thank you Steve Hilton! https://t.co/QaSkw8IWNz
Thank you Katie! https://t.co/uCXoTFTEGm
.@SteveHiltonx “The Democrats statements about Donald Trump are lies. Here are the Facts.” I will soon be posting t… https://t.co/Iu2r5UBODi
Congratulations to Louisiana’s Champions. See you at the White House! https://t.co/Qadi7uD5U4
My Stock Market gains must be judged from the day after the Election, November 9, 2016, where the Market went up bi… https://t.co/4rhdA4J2kO
No, we actually had a very good and productive meeting. Nice! https://t.co/aXeUWcPTc1
In France we are all laughing at how knowingly inaccurate the U.S. reporting of events and conversations at the G-7… https://t.co/LK5quTPeq9
A disgrace! https://t.co/fXss6eixS1
Great meetings at the @G7 in Biarritz, France! #G7Biarritz https://t.co/OdA4SQxUYf
Thank you Eric. So true! https://t.co/9hhVOp2whc
USMCA, make it bipartisan. Everybody wants it! https://t.co/lloDwZr4iN
Jesse &amp; Emma, Great News. Congratulations!!!!! https://t.co/ja7iAN1ypO
Happy Birthday Vince! https://t.co/trOf5Ivmwq
The question I was asked most today by fellow World Leaders, who think the USA is doing so well and is stronger tha… https://t.co/q0VQMrYTSi
Big Trade Deal just agreed to with Prime Minister Abe of Japan. Will be great for our Farmers, Ranchers and more. Really big Corn purchase!
So @donnabrazile gives Crooked Hillary the Questions, and now she’s on @FoxNews!
Rasmussen at 50%. @MediaBuzzFNC &amp; @FoxNews are only getting worse! Now @donnabrazile &amp; others on Fox. Not what it u… https://t.co/di10mmUVO5
Happy Birthday Regis, a truly special man!
Happy Birthday Sean! https://t.co/iQgY6RTWST
Great working breakfast this morning with Prime Minister @BorisJohnson at the Hôtel du Palais in Biarritz, France!… https://t.co/emii9PkdlD
Such False and Inaccurate reporting thus far on the G-7. The Fake News knows this but they can’t help themselves! L… https://t.co/Si4nNUoLEF
....bad Economic times, the worse the better, anything to make my Election more difficult to win. Well, we are havi… https://t.co/r29vbTSqGp
Before I arrived in France, the Fake and Disgusting News was saying that relations with the 6 others countries in t… https://t.co/i2zmu1EZrK
The Media is destroying the Free Press! Mark Levin. So True!
Thank you both. Sooo nice! https://t.co/Fo2CLjc9YZ
France and President @EmmanuelMacron have done a really great job thus far with a very important G-7. Lunch with Em… https://t.co/j0pQVX6SXA
Our great Economy is the talk of everyone!
North Carolina Governor Cooper Vetoed a Bill that would have required Sheriffs to cooperate with Ice. This is a ter… https://t.co/mskDzZ8zOV
Looking forward to helping New York City and Governor @andrewcuomo complete the long anticipated, and partially bui… https://t.co/OV2cERMJqt
Just had lunch with French President @EmmanuelMacron. Many good things are happening for both of our countries. Big… https://t.co/e8VUtgT3Ah
“Face It, You Probably Got A Tax Cut!” This was a New York Times headline, and it is very true. If Republicans take… https://t.co/6G3RfADYvB
....having fun. I was smiling as I looked up and around. The MANY reporters with me were smiling also. They knew th… https://t.co/pdruQtRWwm
When I looked up to the sky and jokingly said “I am the chosen one,” at a press conference two days ago, referring… https://t.co/pDmm3ULisy
For all of the Fake News Reporters that don’t have a clue as to what the law is relative to Presidential powers, Ch… https://t.co/pdIWsorYfC
Such a sad and pathetic fall for @CNN and Jeff Z! https://t.co/vrivSUlDi3
Other good polls also in fifties, despite only Fake News, and then phony polls by A.P., CNN, NBC and, as always, Fo… https://t.co/SOLIpSYfSE
Disgraceful! https://t.co/G4q9Uh1aMc
Thank you Ivanka. Really Amazing! https://t.co/97DAfBsdHu
Looking forward to being with great leaders in France! Leaving soon. https://t.co/hUd66sKFU2
Highest Condolences! Thank you V.P. https://t.co/abydDSlDBw
Great going Harris! https://t.co/KuHQC4F1sz
Great! He said MAGA country did it. So terrible! https://t.co/Vw1xQBZjzN
Thank you to @DiamondandSilk for the really nice words and thoughts on @LouDobbs, tonight hosted by Lou’s friend,… https://t.co/lJJFS8Zorm
Just spoke with President @JairBolsonaro of Brazil. Our future Trade prospects are very exciting and our relationsh… https://t.co/TkVyhghlaJ
...Additionally, the remaining 300 BILLION DOLLARS of goods and products from China, that was being taxed from Sept… https://t.co/m9cSIcFe2i
...unfair Trading Relationship. China should not have put new Tariffs on 75 BILLION DOLLARS of United States produc… https://t.co/KGK8KjkzZX
....Sadly, past Administrations have allowed China to get so far ahead of Fair and Balanced Trade that it has becom… https://t.co/8jsasvADHP
For many years China (and many other countries) has been taking advantage of the United States on Trade, Intellectu… https://t.co/KscBoD4tNm
The Dow is down 573 points perhaps on the news that Representative Seth Moulton, whoever that may be, has dropped o… https://t.co/j3NWi1lbI5
....all deliveries of Fentanyl from China (or anywhere else!). Fentanyl kills 100,000 Americans a year. President X… https://t.co/rpcj6rtQ7i
....your companies HOME and making your products in the USA. I will be responding to China’s Tariffs this afternoon… https://t.co/lg5Do7z58x
....better off without them. The vast amounts of money made and stolen by China from the United States, year after… https://t.co/EOQAANyDYQ
Our Country has lost, stupidly, Trillions of Dollars with China over many years. They have stolen our Intellectual… https://t.co/poBcYLSMOj
....My only question is, who is our bigger enemy, Jay Powell or Chairman Xi?
As usual, the Fed did NOTHING! It is incredible that they can “speak” without knowing or asking what I am doing, wh… https://t.co/6Duw7CUoPG
Now the Fed can show their stuff!
This despite the Fake News and Polls! https://t.co/DksmF8hTr7
..willing to lose their wealth, or a big part of it, just for the possibility of winning the Election. But it won’t… https://t.co/7FLVHnI6ro
The Economy is strong and good, whereas the rest of the world is not doing so well. Despite this the Fake News Medi… https://t.co/zUl4NA9IkC
94% Approval Rating within the  Republican Party. Thank you!
Happy birthday James! https://t.co/nx5yo7ajTt
.@SenCoryGardner has done a fantastic job representing the people of Colorado. He really knows how to win. Strong o… https://t.co/WEcy5ZQOqz
Congratulations to the GREAT Bob Cousy! https://t.co/nNF26OQL6i
Looking forward to soon being in North Carolina to hold a big rally for wonderful Dan Bishop, who is running for Co… https://t.co/FYuQ9CIl7G
Check out a FANTASTIC new book, “STILL WINNING – Why America Went All In On Donald Trump-And Why We Must Do It Agai… https://t.co/O7cdWiLlj9
...I am hopeful Congress will engage with my Team to pass meaningful legislation that will make a real difference a… https://t.co/qae8F9Lgzk
Just concluded a very good meeting on preventing Mass Shootings. Talks are ongoing w/ both Republicans &amp; Democrats.… https://t.co/wlrWfZNKZo
Just heard that Sean Spicer will be on “Dancing with the Stars.” He will do great. A terrific person who loves our Country dearly!
The Economy is doing really well. The Federal Reserve can easily make it Record Setting! The question is being aske… https://t.co/2byVastHVr
Germany sells 30 year bonds offering negative yields. Germany competes with the USA. Our Federal Reserve does not a… https://t.co/xOi1DGGQQm
Thank you @RealWayneRoot! https://t.co/CqjtFbnMVY
It was my honor to sign a Presidential Memorandum facilitating the cancellation of student loan debt for 25K of our… https://t.co/1nadOpO1LW
Great! @LouDobbs interviewed on @seanhannity tonight at 9:00 P.M.  @FoxNews
....that when this Administration’s alternative is no longer available, California will squeeze them to a point of… https://t.co/GD6aA8jNc4
Henry Ford would be very disappointed if he saw his modern-day descendants wanting to build a much more expensive c… https://t.co/DImLvxCfqE
The Legendary Henry Ford and Alfred P. Sloan, the Founders of Ford Motor Company and General Motors, are “rolling o… https://t.co/ljMjHaZre3
“Tax cuts, deregulation, and an Administration dedicated to growing business have allowed the U.S. economy to flour… https://t.co/CPBh2z8rbF
.@NATO, very unfair to the United States! https://t.co/YIgmTkpScU
....Because of me, these countries have agreed to pay ONE HUNDRED BILLION DOLLARS more - but still way short of wha… https://t.co/X3P8flL7fc
For the record, Denmark is only at 1.35% of GDP for NATO spending. They are a wealthy country and should be at 2%.… https://t.co/lVx1c9JmOP
On my way to the Great Commonwealth of Kentucky to deliver remarks at the @AMVETSHQ 75th Annual National Convention… https://t.co/JEcA6uRsax
....WHERE IS THE FEDERAL RESERVE?
So Germany is paying Zero interest and is actually being paid to borrow money, while the U.S., a far stronger and m… https://t.co/Ezrpvcm4R3
My proposal to the politically correct Automobile Companies would lower the average price of a car to consumers by… https://t.co/WIUy5xauO7
.....We are competing with many countries that have a far lower interest rate, and we should be lower than them. Ye… https://t.co/oy1nXArbKw
Doing great with China and other Trade Deals. The only problem we have is Jay Powell and the Fed. He’s like a golfe… https://t.co/CMWhZqhAWb
The Fake News LameStream Media is doing everything possible the “create” a U.S. recession, even though the numbers… https://t.co/M53XRLI9Bx
“The speed bump has been missteps by the Federal Reserve.” @cvpayne  @foxandfriends  So true!
Rep Tlaib wants to cut off aid to Israel. This is the new face the of Democrat Party? Read the AOC PLUS 3 statement… https://t.co/Ga1qfJPNnD
Brandon Judd, President, National Border Patrol Council. “This will effectively end Catch and Release and curb illegal entries.”
.....all Jews, Blacks, Gays, everyone. And importantly, he’s good for everyone in America who wants a job.” Wow!… https://t.co/jYKJfqmCdo
....like he’s the King of Israel. They love him like he is the second coming of God...But American Jews don’t know… https://t.co/6s0DSsIzA0
“Thank you to Wayne Allyn Root for the very nice words. “President Trump is the greatest President for Jews and for… https://t.co/2D8VVvh6jM
....The Prime Minister was able to save a great deal of expense and effort for both the United States and Denmark b… https://t.co/kG39jlNg1P
Denmark is a very special country with incredible people, but based on Prime Minister Mette Frederiksen’s comments,… https://t.co/ygje5jnRIa
CONGRATULATIONS @EricTrump and @LaraLeaTrump, on the birth of Carolina Dorothy Trump. So proud! https://t.co/eSIrFz0zmR
https://t.co/WyGbgUGEhJ
Sorry, I don’t buy Rep. Tlaib’s tears. I have watched her violence, craziness and, most importantly, WORDS, for far… https://t.co/bILTehObEw
The LameStream Media is far beyond Fake News, they are treading in very dangerous territory! https://t.co/J60JgSFhcx
Thank you! https://t.co/LANNJ7IfEl
Just another disgruntled former employee who got fired for gross incompetence! https://t.co/63VhfqQwhx
Ratings are way down, lost all credibility. Beautiful to watch! https://t.co/wO9npDQ2Ys
Maria, despite all of their will and energy, it won’t work! https://t.co/qUTkERCfsv
Thank you Mike! https://t.co/FBcd2OHS6G
Two incredible people. I can’t believe they’re not working (few work harder)! https://t.co/tsh8KDS8Qs
The Fake and Corrupt Media is sooo bad for our Country, The Enemy of the People! https://t.co/GPiklem0u1
Congratulations, Great Show! https://t.co/RrdFQuk99M
Thank you Jon, working hard! https://t.co/R4yrKCcr8x
Nobody ever heard of this dope until he met me. He only lasted 11 days! https://t.co/RzX3zjXzga
I promise not to do this to Greenland! https://t.co/03DdyVU6HA
Thank you to my great supporters at the 2019 @IowaStateFair! https://t.co/83qspei4TP
Great discussion with Prime Minister @BorisJohnson today. We talked about Brexit and how we can move rapidly on a U… https://t.co/NcdJYwykki
Spoke to my two good friends, Prime Minister Modi of India, and Prime Minister Khan of Pakistan, regarding Trade, S… https://t.co/HzfrcnuHNG
THANK YOU! #MAGA https://t.co/hFkXxB18Ra
Massive overflow crowds in New Hampshire last week. Couldn’t get into packed SNHU Arena. Fake and Corrupt News woul… https://t.co/7JZm20pC89
Wow, Report Just Out! Google manipulated from 2.6 million to 16 million votes for Hillary Clinton in 2016 Election!… https://t.co/59flWJFiVE
.....The Fed Rate, over a fairly short period of time, should be reduced by at least 100 basis points, with perhaps… https://t.co/UYCqLcZbsP
Our Economy is very strong, despite the horrendous lack of vision by Jay Powell and the Fed, but the Democrats are… https://t.co/ddvKYChbaZ
Democrats want Open Borders and Crime! So dangerous for our Country. But we are building a big, beautiful, NEW Wall… https://t.co/P8HKImJfKu
....got fired. Wrote a very nice book about me just recently. Now the book is a lie? Said his wife was driving him… https://t.co/SHbmoVb5fS
Anthony Scaramucci is a highly unstable “nut job” who was with other candidates in the primary who got shellacked,… https://t.co/kppQGbYmQx
Great cohesion inside the Republican Party, the best I have ever seen. Despite all of the Fake News, my Poll Number… https://t.co/FqFkV3id14
The New York Times will be out of business soon after I leave office, hopefully in 6 years. They have Zero credibil… https://t.co/pG16GK55tW
Thank you @TedCruz, I couldn’t agree more! https://t.co/MGq0xXin0s
House Democrats want to take action against Israel because it is fighting back against two (maybe four) people that… https://t.co/XjMIhiOA63
Our economy is the best in the world, by far. Lowest unemployment ever within almost all categories. Poised for big… https://t.co/ltnEpWZB1w
Juan Williams at @FoxNews is so pathetic, and yet when he met me in the Fox Building lobby, he couldn’t have been n… https://t.co/2AhJzC7FS7
We are doing very well with China, and talking!
Doing really well! https://t.co/UndcviEiML
MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
With all that this Administration has accomplished, think what my Poll Numbers would be if we had an honest Media, which we do not!
.....”Journalism” has reached a new low in the history of our Country. It is nothing more than an evil propaganda m… https://t.co/LKFxW5HD7K
The Failing New York Times, in one of the most devastating portrayals of bad journalism in history, got caught by a… https://t.co/BIyVs3Xid4
Such a disgrace at the once great @nytimes! https://t.co/UKjP6AU0hz
Thank you! https://t.co/tG32CxB1LQ
The Fake News Media HATES to see this! https://t.co/VMgyggOQ3Q
Thank you to @SaraCarterDC. A great and legitimate reporter, as opposed to those at the Failing New York Times! https://t.co/oM7vEvt9xO
Major consideration is being given to naming ANTIFA an “ORGANIZATION OF TERROR.” Portland is being watched very clo… https://t.co/W2uvDB4NNZ
Biggest crowd EVER, according to Arena people. Thousands outside trying to get in. Place was packed! Radical Left D… https://t.co/yxIR59J9zs
Look at the tremendous overflow at packed arena in New Hampshire last night. Sorry we couldn’t get you in, will be… https://t.co/mslfbJt15u
Great time in New Hampshire last night. Placed was maxed out, totally packed, with thousands coming to the arena fl… https://t.co/E5Gg3F1X5x
Having dinner tonight with Tim Cook of Apple. They will be spending vast sums of money in the U.S. Great!
Just completed a very good meeting on Afghanistan. Many on the opposite side of this 19 year war, and us, are looki… https://t.co/BUrHrUyyKy
I donate 100% of my President’s salary, $400,000, back to our Country, and feel very good about it! https://t.co/cX8Op2qyw7
Like it or not, Tlaib and Omar are fast becoming the face of the Democrat Party. Cortez (AOC) is fuming, not happy about this!
Rep. Tlaib wrote a letter to Israeli officials desperately wanting to visit her grandmother. Permission was quickly… https://t.co/hd6UmYsquv
Israel was very respectful &amp; nice to Rep. Rashida Tlaib, allowing her permission to visit her “grandmother.” As soo… https://t.co/GAT9W7IxbD
https://t.co/9WNq9PtnFY
https://t.co/fJPpaVmLUZ
Senator Jim Risch of the Great State of Idaho has been an incredible supporter of our Agenda! He is tough on Crime,… https://t.co/dcWrCIXB3p
Congratulations to Patrick Yoes for his election as National President of the great Fraternal Order of Police. Toge… https://t.co/NkulKy0HaY
Thank you to my good friend Chuck Canterbury for 16 years of service to the Fraternal Order of Police and our great… https://t.co/Hw6WRSEE2U
A great evening, with incredible people, in New Hampshire! https://t.co/XvqQCgorIW
Thank you Rudy! https://t.co/u0InDTYA9f
Great news! Tonight, we broke the all-time attendance record previously held by Elton John at #SNHUArena in Manches… https://t.co/BoVlcVgcHQ
Thank you New Hampshire. KEEP AMERICA GREAT! #KAG2020 https://t.co/fbU7YYsYyI
https://t.co/TCg6dLoIya
Walmart, a great indicator as to how the U.S. is doing, just released outstanding numbers. Our Country, unlike othe… https://t.co/RleZ8PpGBV
“If they don’t get this Trade Deal with the U.S. done, China could have it first recession (or worse!) in years. Th… https://t.co/D9paA7KieM
Sadly, much truth to this! https://t.co/KG9HNbyrZh
Andrew, thank you! We will never forgive or forget. https://t.co/giSOLlCckV
Biden doesn’t have a clue! I will solve the China problem. https://t.co/v0sAoVEAoB
The Fake News Media is doing everything they can to crash the economy because they think that will be bad for me an… https://t.co/irIShkIHM3
Representatives Omar and Tlaib are the face of the Democrat Party, and they HATE Israel!
Wow! The Deputy Editor of the Failing New York Times was just demoted. Should have been Fired! Totally biased and i… https://t.co/BPnbmpvapd
Our Great Farmers know how important it is to win on Trade. They will be the big winners!
The United States is now, by far, the Biggest, Strongest and Most Powerful Economy in the World, it is not even clo… https://t.co/4yaZquNZRw
If President Xi would meet directly and personally with the protesters, there would be a happy and enlightened endi… https://t.co/z2rJaqjyjj
It would show great weakness if Israel allowed Rep. Omar and Rep.Tlaib to visit. They hate Israel &amp; all Jewish peop… https://t.co/ifxrF8rKdT
The Philadelphia shooter should never have been allowed to be on the streets. He had a long and very dangerous crim… https://t.co/m8OKxGnmth
....what they were doing. There’s plenty of indication, we don’t have to speculate.” @SteveDoocy “Holy cow, got to… https://t.co/UczUdYguRC
Go out and get Andrew McCarthy’s new book, “Ball of Collusion.” “Supervision became the investigator, and when they… https://t.co/3uexrosde2
Thank you, and the Wall is under major construction! https://t.co/jRVMxSPJzN
Two great entertainers and, more importantly, great people! Check out their show. https://t.co/SGmbEeJuIM
I know President Xi of China very well. He is a great leader who very much has the respect of his people. He is als… https://t.co/5cpiEfnhdk
..deferral to December. It actually helps China more than us, but will be reciprocated. Millions of jobs are being… https://t.co/1Jc72Bh2Tx
Good things were stated on the call with China the other day. They are eating the Tariffs with the devaluation of t… https://t.co/svFXQxuqyD
Sad! https://t.co/CP9azm8U54
Unlike others, our economy is strong! https://t.co/EvNRzB8GBY
..Spread is way too much as other countries say THANK YOU to clueless Jay Powell and the Federal Reserve. Germany,… https://t.co/J6Zm3iXb78
We are winning, big time, against China. Companies &amp; jobs are fleeing. Prices to us have not gone up, and in some c… https://t.co/F0S9BfIY12
The Great Charles Payne @cvpayne correctly stated that Fed Chair Jay Powell made TWO enormous mistakes. 1. When he… https://t.co/6moIF2h3pv
Tremendous amounts of money pouring into the United States. People want safety!
“So far, you’ve had Tariffs imposed on 300 Billion Dollars worth of Chinese products, but you can’t tell me that it… https://t.co/mn8ZjS6V7k
“The Fed has got to do something! The Fed is the Central Bank of the United States, not the Central Bank of the Wor… https://t.co/20dGjklub3
Join me tomorrow night in Manchester, New Hampshire at 7:00 P.M. Eastern! #KAG2020 https://t.co/0UViqSlLgd
A fighter and champion, GREAT! https://t.co/8LoTrb6Pdc
Great interview of Ron Vitiello, Former Acting Ice Director, by @JesseBWatters, on @FoxNews, about all of the work… https://t.co/T3a9rZvam7
Great day in the incredible Commonwealth of Pennsylvania today, with the amazing energy workers, construction worke… https://t.co/dnTgYCKXVJ
No debate on Election Security should go forward without first agreeing that Voter ID (Identification) must play a… https://t.co/10AIANOJ37
Thank you Bill! https://t.co/6TwDUEB7xm
True! Without being stuck at an airport, where CNN buys (at a big price) an uninterested audience, they’ve got noth… https://t.co/M1jjGzCZzU
It always happens! When a Conservative does even a fraction of what Chris Cuomo did with his lunatic ranting, ravin… https://t.co/nY25cmqpCz
See you in New Hampshire! https://t.co/NhY0QwRrkd
Just leaving. Incredible Complex. JOBS! JOBS! JOBS! https://t.co/culShq7aqi
So terrible! https://t.co/L9lqQIGAUp
Put it back up. We are living with a Rigged &amp; Fake Media! https://t.co/ZhanbGCxuX
Just landed in Pennsylvania. Looking forward to making a speech on energy. So important!
Our Intelligence has informed us that the Chinese Government is moving troops to the Border with Hong Kong. Everyon… https://t.co/6VkK8eOQY1
Many are blaming me, and the United States, for the problems going on in Hong Kong. I can’t imagine why?
ALL THE NEWS THAT’S NOT FIT TO PRINT! “The New York Times is no longer the paper we grew up with. It is no longer a… https://t.co/aqRuhs3sMt
As usual, China said they were going to be buying “big” from our great American Farmers. So far they have not done… https://t.co/yRfMWeh6Lu
Would Chris Cuomo be given a Red Flag for his recent rant? Filthy language and a total loss of control. He shouldn’… https://t.co/NbNU9CpuhI
Thank you Steve! https://t.co/4qwvkUTg5t
Through massive devaluation of their currency and pumping vast sums of money into their system, the tens of billion… https://t.co/TXpVRHpxSs
I thought Chris was Fredo also. The truth hurts. Totally lost it! Low ratings @CNN https://t.co/yBpGjt4N1T
Thank you John, you are a special guy! https://t.co/yAtCFcNeDL
Curt Schilling, a great pitcher and patriot, is considering a run for Congress in Arizona. Terrific!  @foxandfriends
The United States is learning much from the failed missile explosion in Russia. We have similar, though more advanc… https://t.co/vV30xKIVtz
Two great and loyal friends! https://t.co/Fo2CLjc9YZ
Scaramucci, who like so many others had nothing to do with my Election victory, is only upset that I didn’t want hi… https://t.co/KwKEr873PB
Thank you NEGOP! https://t.co/S5A24nleW8
Many incredible things are happening right now for our Country. After years of being ripped off by other nations on… https://t.co/wXJZVMYJhw
..TV talent. Then, during the 2016 Election, I would watch as Joe Scarborough &amp; his very angry Psycho wife(?) would… https://t.co/OQXSIgZ2nn
So funny to watch Little Donny Deutsch on TV with his own failing show. When I did The Apprentice, Donny would call… https://t.co/HAmGUAYf4x
.....other than the fact that this Administration has probably done more than any other Administration in its first… https://t.co/bleeA6tCtf
Anthony Scaramucci, who was quickly terminated (11 days) from a position that he was totally incapable of handling,… https://t.co/0FjMogPhP4
Joe Biden just said, “We believe in facts, not truth.” Does anybody really believe he is mentally fit to be preside… https://t.co/3Y9m957i17
Think how wonderful it is to be able to fight back and show, to so many, how totally dishonest the Fake News Media… https://t.co/nztWMMdcbz
China wants to make a deal so badly. Thousands of companies are leaving because of the Tariffs, they must stem the… https://t.co/lGSG4qW2jS
....cause big disruption by going to Manhattan. Working almost all of the time, including evenings. Don’t have to b… https://t.co/9wpMgX8SfW
Got to see, by accident, wacko comedian Bill Maher’s show - So many lies. He said patients in El Paso hospital didn… https://t.co/goJNe8AWDQ
Never has the press been more inaccurate, unfair or corrupt! We are not fighting the Democrats, they are easy, we a… https://t.co/xltGI6mLJC
....also a small apology for testing the short range missiles, and that this testing would stop when the exercises… https://t.co/ZEY1TIcdrd
In a letter to me sent by Kim Jong Un, he stated, very nicely, that he would like to meet and start negotiations as… https://t.co/PwvIPqQAzU
Maggie Haberman of the Failing @nytimes reported that I was annoyed by the lack of cameras inside the hospitals in… https://t.co/6sp6dxT6ZM
....to inflame and cause chaos. They create their own violence, and then try to blame others. They are the true Rac… https://t.co/r6f1K8zGkk
Liberal Hollywood is Racist at the highest level, and with great Anger and Hate! They like to call themselves “Elit… https://t.co/BLZAStZXwA
....mentally ill or deranged people. I am the biggest Second Amendment person there is, but we all must work togeth… https://t.co/T9OthUAsXe
Serious discussions are taking place between House and Senate leadership  on meaningful Background Checks. I have a… https://t.co/sPiAnbdoaK
Rod Blagojevich, the former Governor of Illinois, was sentenced to 14 years in prison. He has served 7 years. Many… https://t.co/5wEDXYgHVQ
....career in the military, retiring from the U.S. Navy in 2010. He commanded at every level, including the Naval S… https://t.co/Ny7OUAzL1n
I am pleased to inform you that the Honorable Joseph Maguire, current Director of the National Counterterrorism Cen… https://t.co/9wemgG0spy
....coincides with the retirement of Dan Coats. A new Acting Director of National Intelligence will be named shortly.
Sue Gordon is a great professional with a long and distinguished career. I have gotten to know Sue over the past 2… https://t.co/LXgzwLDW24
....I know Emmanuel means well, as do all others, but nobody speaks for the United States but the United States its… https://t.co/qLCrHlaoKi
Iran is in serious financial trouble. They want desperately to talk to the U.S., but are given mixed signals from a… https://t.co/u88KbSurnS
....in the world, there is nobody even close, but unfortunately the same cannot be said about our Federal Reserve.… https://t.co/CqhSmQ3cMK
....John Deere, our car companies, &amp; others, to compete on a level playing field. With substantial Fed Cuts (there… https://t.co/GwLMofZIsI
As your President, one would think that I would be thrilled with our very strong dollar. I am not! The Fed’s high i… https://t.co/4SQBx5KKrc
....I am so amazed that MSNBC &amp; CNN can keep putting on, over and over again, people that have no idea what I am al… https://t.co/1aF1mkzgTe
Just watched a world class loser, Tim O’Brien, who I haven’t seen or spoken to in many years, &amp; knows NOTHING about… https://t.co/FokunCKngA
My time spent in Dayton and El Paso with some of the greatest people on earth. Thank you for a job well done! https://t.co/TNVDGhxOpo
Incredible afternoon in El Paso, Texas. We love you, and are with you, all the way! https://t.co/pTNhHapx86
The Dems new weapon is actually their old weapon, one which they never cease to use when they are down, or run out… https://t.co/Tew1HO5Lzq
Leaving El Paso for the White House. What GREAT people I met there and in Dayton, Ohio. The Fake News worked overti… https://t.co/ankLOw5aTq
I don’t know who Joaquin Castro is other than the lesser brother of a failed presidential candidate (1%) who makes… https://t.co/4vkvc2594N
https://t.co/RCcXfhUwP3
The people I met today in Dayton are the finest anywhere! https://t.co/sBxKZWExcR
We love you Dayton, Ohio! https://t.co/IaCZAdyuzL
Watching Fake News CNN is better than watching Shepard Smith, the lowest rated show on @FoxNews. Actually, whenever… https://t.co/p0d2DHLdG5
....misrepresenting what took place inside of the hospital. Their news conference after I left for El Paso was a fr… https://t.co/mZ4usW2PvJ
Just left Dayton, Ohio, where I met with the Victims &amp; families, Law Enforcement, Medical Staff &amp; First Responders.… https://t.co/6wNWXBLhUX
Watching Sleepy Joe Biden making a speech. Sooo Boring! The LameStream Media will die in the ratings and clicks wit… https://t.co/uukgq76lkP
Today, we honor all of our Country’s Purple Heart recipients, their loved ones, and our Gold Star Families for thei… https://t.co/kjeha7aZsA
....terrible thing to watch, especially when things could be taken care of sooo easily. We will WIN anyway, but it… https://t.co/H2HglrDJxV
....proud to admit their mistake of acting too fast and tightening too much (and that I was right!). They must Cut… https://t.co/s4To9GHDxl
“Three more Central Banks cut rates.” Our problem is not China - We are stronger than ever, money is pouring into t… https://t.co/efBOM0XST0
“Meanwhile, the Dayton, Ohio, shooter had a history of supporting political figures like Bernie Sanders, Elizabeth… https://t.co/OBANU8Ajyf
..”This is an astounding development in journalism. I’ve never seen it happen before, I’ve just never seen anything… https://t.co/WPgBYek0v4
“Trump Urges Unity Vs. Racism,” was the correct description in the first headline by the Failing New York Times, bu… https://t.co/FTfOElLqMK
...Talks have begun to further increase payments to the United States. South Korea is a very wealthy nation that no… https://t.co/B7m3zhQdku
South Korea has agreed to pay substantially more money to the United States in order to defend itself from North Ko… https://t.co/c4jtb17fHb
Beto (phony name to indicate Hispanic heritage) O’Rourke, who is embarrassed by my last visit to the Great State of… https://t.co/gxpUZt91iq
....Amendment.” John Yoo. @IngrahamAngle  Former Governor Jerry Brown vetoed the same bill in that it was ridiculou… https://t.co/wS9sR61KgK
“California is trying to meddle with a ballot in order to oppose President Trump, and it’s clearly something Califo… https://t.co/NT4u3aiA2Y
Will be going to Dayton, Ohio and El Paso, Texas, tomorrow to meet with First Responders, Law Enforcement, and some… https://t.co/Po4BxtiEcp
...in 2020.” Lou Dobbs stated that this is a fraud on the American public. @peterschweizer stated with certainty th… https://t.co/PVW4FAq6Qa
... are NOT planning to illegally subvert the 2020 Election despite all that has been said to the contrary. It all… https://t.co/1aAMA0usG1
.@sundarpichai of Google was in the Oval Office working very hard to explain how much he liked me, what a great job… https://t.co/qLjwg18njC
Thank you @JimCramer @CNBC! https://t.co/DW7HDA0WEK
Thank you Mr. Wonderful, I like you too! @kevinolearytv @CNBC https://t.co/8n5qcTVSp2
As they have learned in the last two years, our great American Farmers know that China will not be able to hurt the… https://t.co/qlBy5ZKcJj
Massive amounts of money from China and other parts of the world is pouring into the United States for reasons of s… https://t.co/8TrQGOQj8g
“It’s political season and the election is around the corner. They want to continue to push that racist narrative.”… https://t.co/1bAr6QNeEF
“Did George Bush ever condemn President Obama after Sandy Hook. President Obama had 32 mass shootings during his re… https://t.co/4BqF1NB5Ro
Thank you @PeterSchweizer! https://t.co/TZxmiouWOm
Check out what @Google is up to for the 2020 election! #KAG2020 https://t.co/roM2WNmUSP
Thank you @LouDobbs and Tom Homan! https://t.co/VC1oNdcLEy
We must honor the sacred memory of those we have lost by acting as ONE PEOPLE. Open wounds cannot heal if we are di… https://t.co/CCTzzz63mq
Today, I am also directing the Department of Justice to propose legislation ensuring that those who commit hate cri… https://t.co/7Iukhh0FuO
The First Lady and I join all Americans in praying and grieving for the victims, their families, and the survivors.… https://t.co/EN0q2294VI
China is intent on continuing to receive the hundreds of Billions of Dollars they have been taking from the U.S. wi… https://t.co/gDeAZNBwny
....used currency manipulation to steal our businesses and factories, hurt our jobs, depress our workers’ wages and… https://t.co/UUdKKRsePC
Based on the historic currency manipulation by China, it is now even more obvious to everyone that Americans are no… https://t.co/nXanUnjNXA
China dropped the price of their currency to an almost a historic low. It’s called “currency manipulation.” Are you… https://t.co/EP6FqVhE9b
The Media has a big responsibility to life and safety in our Country. Fake News has contributed greatly to the ange… https://t.co/0qoxJBDezb
....this legislation with desperately needed immigration reform. We must have something good, if not GREAT, come ou… https://t.co/RgrBOhEU9F
We cannot let those killed in El Paso, Texas, and Dayton, Ohio, die in vain. Likewise for those so seriously wounde… https://t.co/ISrVfymkUJ
....The flags at the White House will be lowered today through Thursday, August 8. Melania and I are praying for al… https://t.co/3LtJlWada4
Today, I authorized the lowering of the flags to half-staff at all Federal Government buildings in honor of the vic… https://t.co/IgDFEyGquV
God bless the people of El Paso, Texas. God bless the people of Dayton, Ohio.
The FBI, local and state law enforcement are working together in El Paso and in Dayton, Ohio. Information is rapidl… https://t.co/2e55C7Amlo
....Melania and I send our heartfelt thoughts and prayers to the great people of Texas.
Today’s shooting in El Paso, Texas, was not only tragic, it was an act of cowardice. I know that I stand with every… https://t.co/5FHgnbcuDf
'God be with you all': Trump pledges full support for El Paso shooting victims as lawmakers also grieve… https://t.co/yyAEBxjNXC
Pastor Scott, a great guy - and tough! https://t.co/tu0u3AxQqp
Fight hard tonight Colby. You are a real Champ! #MAGA https://t.co/dj3JlWQu7i
Terrible shootings in ElPaso, Texas. Reports are very bad, many killed. Working with State and Local authorities, a… https://t.co/p9I5Pnj6ej
Things are going along very well with China. They are paying us Tens of Billions of Dollars, made possible by their… https://t.co/LGLPqyYJ0w
Countries are coming to us wanting to negotiate REAL trade deals, not the one sided horror show deals made by past… https://t.co/eMfR3G1jid
Great working with you John. A big win for our amazing ranchers! https://t.co/m2PjlbTHA9
A great couple! https://t.co/h0o1laZ7e3
Nice to see that one of my best pupils is still a giant Trump fan. Steve joined me after I won the primaries, but I… https://t.co/191Op8GGHw
....John has therefore decided to stay in Congress where he has done such an outstanding job representing the peopl… https://t.co/fZHW0eo1Zr
Our great Republican Congressman John Ratcliffe is being treated very unfairly by the LameStream Media. Rather than… https://t.co/HMqCr55cJ9
A$AP Rocky released from prison and on his way home to the United States from Sweden. It was a Rocky Week, get home ASAP A$AP!
....Chariman Kim has a great and beautiful vision for his country, and only the United States, with me as President… https://t.co/Nn56xpzKr2
.....Chairman Kim does not want to disappoint me with a violation of trust, there is far too much for North Korea t… https://t.co/TjKmKTYyav
Kim Jong Un and North Korea tested 3 short range missiles over the last number of days. These missiles tests are no… https://t.co/anL3BsX2f6
Really bad news! The Baltimore house of Elijah Cummings was robbed. Too bad!
THANK YOU OHIO!! #KAG2020 https://t.co/UF6b1sdC4r
I would like to thank two Great Iowa Senators, @ChuckGrassley and @SenJoniErnst - for their support today on the Sp… https://t.co/seK0ONSgsg
Beautiful evening in Cincinnati, Ohio tonight — with GREAT American Patriots! #KAG2020 https://t.co/wDN5B4Gp87
Thank you Cincinnati, Ohio. Together, we are going to KEEP AMERICA GREAT! https://t.co/sKPAW8e8qN
https://t.co/cbw3KXwvES
...We look forward to continuing our positive dialogue with China on a comprehensive Trade Deal, and feel that the… https://t.co/04vCkhSUG1
...during the talks the U.S. will start, on September 1st, putting a small additional Tariff of 10% on the remainin… https://t.co/9uHUs91afm
...buy agricultural product from the U.S. in large quantities, but did not do so. Additionally, my friend President… https://t.co/Dt2e5SIGd1
Our representatives have just returned from China where they had constructive talks having to do with a future Trad… https://t.co/LsYihbltRg
https://t.co/0Zx9wr3MoP
"A string of court cases that have been run through the legal system that have hit DEAD ENDS...." @BillHemmer… https://t.co/f3pvIAyBE8
https://t.co/It3T0ANlrs
BIG RALLY tonight in Cincinnati, Ohio. See you there! P.S. Our Country is doing GREAT!
Budget Deal is phenomenal for our Great Military, our Vets, and Jobs, Jobs, Jobs! Two year deal gets us past the El… https://t.co/9xo9Ge7Dti
China, Iran &amp; other foreign countries are looking at the Democrat Candidates and “drooling” over the small prospect… https://t.co/d0qFekiQv1
Congratulations to Kelly Knight Craft of #Kentucky on her confirmation as United Nations Ambassador. After having s… https://t.co/PUK0czF95v
...It will soon be time to choose to keep and build upon that prosperity and success, or let it go. We are respecte… https://t.co/snadutVxxO
The people on the stage tonight, and last, were not those that will either Make America Great Again or Keep America… https://t.co/f12Gqo4ILb
The cages for kids were built by the Obama Administration in 2014. He had the policy of child separation. I ended i… https://t.co/WMAfEMjwvv
Experts stated that the Fed should not have tightened, and then waited too long to undo their mistake. James Bullar… https://t.co/UKa9el1lWR
Very low ratings for the Democratic Debate last night — they’re desperate for Trump!
Thank you Bill, say hello to our GREAT VETERANS! https://t.co/toDqIAIQ54
The Radical Left Dems went after me for using the words “drug-infested” concerning Baltimore. Take a look at Elijah… https://t.co/Z11wCzzgGB
“The 99% Get a Bigger Raise” https://t.co/negNLaSwMt
....As usual, Powell let us down, but at least he is ending quantitative tightening, which shouldn’t have started i… https://t.co/knw2FP0Eni
What the Market wanted to hear from Jay Powell and the Federal Reserve was that this was the beginning of a lengthy… https://t.co/TLR23NXwAz
....I am very happy for Eddie Gallagher and his family!
....to information that may have been obtained from opposing lawyers and for giving immunity in a totally incompete… https://t.co/SE8wpL6CsS
The Prosecutors who lost the case against SEAL Eddie Gallagher (who I released from solitary confinement so he coul… https://t.co/hW4qgEv2mC
....or is he too dumb (stupid} to understand that. No wonder CNN’s ratings (MSNBC’s also) have gone down the tubes… https://t.co/OSWIDodI7K
CNN’s Don Lemon, the dumbest man on television, insinuated last night while asking a debate “question” that I was a… https://t.co/9MqfpVD9x8
Lowering drug prices for many Americans - including our great seniors! At my direction, @HHSGov @SecAzar just relea… https://t.co/SKhMUfvtmI
“The lesser of two Socialists is still a Socialist!” Senator John Kennedy of Louisiana
If I hadn’t won the 2016 Election, we would be in a Great Recession/Depression right now. The people I saw on stage… https://t.co/YG9PJsusiM
Such a great victory in court yesterday on the Russian Hoax, the greatest political scam in the history of our Coun… https://t.co/ttNruQgudA
....vindication &amp; exoneration from the Russian, WikiLeaks and every other form of HOAX perpetrated by the DNC, Radi… https://t.co/yrjqfKtbGY
Wow! A federal Judge in the Southern District of N.Y. completely dismissed a lawsuit brought by the Democratic Nati… https://t.co/8Qty1JaK93
https://t.co/sPd4GF6wxu
Thank you Eric! https://t.co/Cq2w0we6kp
Thank you Amy! https://t.co/NiwkdBGVA9
We should immediately pass Voter ID @Voteridplease to insure the safety and sanctity of our voting system. Also, Pa… https://t.co/3WPmOMJoRo
Great reception in Jamestown by both REPUBLICANS &amp; DEMOCRATS. Respect for our Country’s incredible Heritage. Thank you!
Heading to Jamestown, Virginia. Word is the Democrats will make it as uncomfortable as possible, but that’s ok beca… https://t.co/HGiii2Sfn5
....Don’t watch show, but heard Mika said I asked to preside over their marriage. Not true—does anyone really belie… https://t.co/tKzzfRIyaD
Just reminded my staff that Morning Joe &amp; Psycho were with me in my room, at their request, the night I won New Ham… https://t.co/h5j349ZkGv
China has lost 5 million jobs and two million manufacturing jobs due to the Trump Tariffs. Trumps got China back on… https://t.co/mBw7F0ftKQ
Senate is working hard on America’s Transportation Infrastructure Act. Will have BIG IMPACT on our highways and roa… https://t.co/6fvmOgJUJB
....@foxandfriends
Wow! Morning Joe &amp; Psycho ratings have really crashed. Very small audience. People are tired of hearing Fake News d… https://t.co/UtIc2v8yIw
...to ripoff the USA, even bigger and better than ever before. The problem with them waiting, however, is that if &amp;… https://t.co/m8Ll0r8jP1
..My team is negotiating with them now, but they always change the deal in the end to their benefit. They should pr… https://t.co/Oz8toIwVsa
China is doing very badly, worst year in 27 - was supposed to start buying our agricultural product now - no signs… https://t.co/P5IZSWbosI
Despite the Democrats wanting very unsafe Open Borders &amp; refusing to change the Loopholes &amp; Asylum, tremendous prog… https://t.co/PlomJ42ToP
Somali refugees arresed in Tucson on way to Egypt. They were in touch with an agent posing as a terrorist. One of t… https://t.co/dfcCEsgZXI
“I don’t know what it’s going to take. A lot of Democratic run cities all over America look like this, it’s not jus… https://t.co/xd96b3Fp02
Baltimore’s numbers are the worst in the United States on Crime and the Economy. Billions of dollars have been pump… https://t.co/8mYWBiEs51
Elijah Cummings never even went to the Southern Border and then he screams at the very good people who, despite Con… https://t.co/L9rxsd4vCk
....She loves our Military and our Vets and protects our Second Amendment. Cindy has my Full and Total Endorsement! #MAGA
Senator Cindy Hyde-Smith is doing a GREAT JOB for the people of Mississippi and fully supports our #MAGA Agenda. Ci… https://t.co/nAC0DZwySE
Just remember, the Iranians never won a war, but never lost a negotiation!
....He is tough on Crime, Strong on Borders, and will fight for our Second Amendment. Daniel will never let you dow… https://t.co/Tlqqt6X8EO
The Republican Party has a new STAR, his name is Daniel Cameron (@djaycameron), and he is running for Attorney Gene… https://t.co/UpP3dfqBOK
It is the 25th Anniversary of a GREAT Organization run by people who truly love our Country, @JudicialWatch. On beh… https://t.co/HFCWOPNGH5
Looking forward to my meeting at 2:00 P.M. with wonderful Inner City Pastors!
....countries that know how to play the game against the U.S. That’s actually why the E.U. was formed....and for Ch… https://t.co/uUvSkA31cL
The Fed “raised” way too early and way too much. Their quantitative tightening was another big mistake. While our C… https://t.co/F9wogOrZ8O
....even to new heights of success and glory, but not with King Elijah and that crew. When the leaders of Baltimore… https://t.co/hwPEup4pv8
Crazy Bernie Sanders recently equated the City of Baltimore to a THIRD WORLD COUNTRY! Based on that statement, I as… https://t.co/lepXZsfmDT
The E.U. and China will further lower interest rates and pump money into their systems, making it much easier for t… https://t.co/jBIYciTUDT
Al Sharpton would always ask me to go to his events. He would say, “it’s a personal favor to me.” Seldom, but somet… https://t.co/9nb3XmdMyG
If the Democrats are going to defend the Radical Left “Squad” and King Elijah’s Baltimore Fail, it will be a long r… https://t.co/DptfkkM1cW
Baltimore, under the leadership of Elijah Cummings, has the worst Crime Statistics in the Nation. 25 years of all t… https://t.co/NpnGnCObD8
I have known Al for 25 years. Went to fights with him &amp; Don King, always got along well. He “loved Trump!” He would… https://t.co/FXgML5zDtu
Good luck with the book George, should do well! https://t.co/Rdti0VyFLd
Law Enforcement is at the scene of shootings in Gilroy, California. Reports are that shooter has not yet been appre… https://t.co/MYxjZozcbW
“The Democrats hate this President so much, they’re forgetting about their duty to secure our Border.”… https://t.co/Ii0ireG7s1
“If the Democrats would have closed the Loopholes two years ago when President Trump asked them to do so, none of t… https://t.co/rOgzAkgEga
....be leaving office on August 15th. I would like to thank Dan for his great service to our Country. The Acting Di… https://t.co/THWZHt8KiQ
I am pleased to announce that highly respected Congressman John Ratcliffe of Texas will be nominated by me to be th… https://t.co/61T0iNf231
Under the Trump Administration, African American unemployment is the lowest (best) in the history of the United Sta… https://t.co/y0GM8Y3Mvz
If racist Elijah Cummings would focus more of his energy on helping the good people of his district, and Baltimore… https://t.co/Qco3AGoiwI
There is nothing racist in stating plainly what most people already know, that Elijah Cummings has done a terrible… https://t.co/EJMU0RvPu0
“Elijah Cummings has had his chance to address it (crime &amp; conditions in Baltimore) for decades, and he hasn’t gott… https://t.co/6GNQ1OteUO
Speaking of failing badly, has anyone seen what is happening to Nancy Pelosi’s district in San Francisco. It is not… https://t.co/8xij0qPH2O
....a look, the facts speak far louder than words! The Democrats always play the Race Card, when in fact they have… https://t.co/tYJ0hBwAOU
Someone please explain to Nancy Pelosi, who was recently called racist by those in her own party, that there is not… https://t.co/J4JM0lb46v
“If it weren’t for Donald Trump, we would never know how corrupt these Democrats are, we would never know for sure… https://t.co/KfwdP6LdPd
https://t.co/9jgdUE5BF8
The Democrats are still doing the Russians dirty work as they continue to push the fake crime. Media credibility is… https://t.co/KSEUQWGJPq
The real Collusion, the Conspiracy, the Crime, was between the Clinton Campaign, the DNC, Fusion GPS, Christopher S… https://t.co/mUQuevwVPm
So sad that Elijah Cummings has been able to do so little for the people of Baltimore. Statistically, Baltimore ran… https://t.co/AMJ2VwCXQd
....Robert Mueller’s testimony, and the Mueller Report itself, was a disaster for this illegal Democrat inspired Wi… https://t.co/itIrYrUCBZ
“One of the biggest things to come out of Mueller’s testimony was the fact that when he was asked, was there ANYTHI… https://t.co/9ELIfIaM60
Thank you @MarkLevinShow! https://t.co/G3f6QBNSMa
https://t.co/9fnYIzjKQX
Thank you @GOPLeader! https://t.co/v7sQt7DDWK
Thanks @JudgeJeanine! https://t.co/chj7JPbWo1
.@RepCummings — your district! https://t.co/JV4SF8ykCT
.@RepCummings, why don’t you focus on your district!? https://t.co/F3Ej0Z21PZ
NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION, TOTAL EXONERATION. DEMOCRAT WITCH HUNT!
We gave Nadler and his Trump hating Dems the complete Mueller Report (we didn’t have to), and even Mueller himself,… https://t.co/pVuESK5W26
Elijah Cummings spends all of his time trying to hurt innocent people through “Oversight.” He does NOTHING for his… https://t.co/jt4YsoX6Gr
Democrats don’t care about Border Security. They refuse to give the votes necessary to fix the Loopholes and Asylum… https://t.co/7BNriGaaMc
Such a big victory of our Country! “Supreme Court approves Trump Administration plan to use Military Funds for the… https://t.co/jFHiJAstT8
The Dems are now coming out of shock from the terrible Mueller performance, and are starting to spin impeachment al… https://t.co/3GICmxao5t
The Democrats were trying mightily to revive the badly &amp; irrevocably tarnished Witch Hunt Hoax until Robert Mueller… https://t.co/ir6kFQnFtA
Consideration is being given to declaring ANTIFA, the gutless Radical Left Wack Jobs who go around hitting (only no… https://t.co/7qTHqxKXTd
Why is so much money sent to the Elijah Cummings district when it is considered the worst run and most dangerous an… https://t.co/O358G0UX84
....As proven last week during a Congressional tour, the Border is clean, efficient &amp; well run, just very crowded.… https://t.co/5NEW7Thmxu
Rep, Elijah Cummings has been a brutal bully, shouting and screaming at the great men &amp; women of Border Patrol abou… https://t.co/7svlPwKJu5
https://t.co/9jgdUE5BF8
Wow! Big VICTORY on the Wall. The United States Supreme Court overturns lower court injunction, allows Southern Bor… https://t.co/RMYYsySDpB
https://t.co/nr9bDv3Ktq
“@DHSgov @DHSMcAleenan Puts Guatemalan Migrants on Fast Track Home” https://t.co/SrkbGqsqvv
The WTO is BROKEN when the world’s RICHEST countries claim to be developing countries to avoid WTO rules and get sp… https://t.co/ABuRFn8pLk
Great morning at the Pentagon yesterday. Congratulations to our new Defense Secretary, Mark @EsperDoD! https://t.co/zqtA4XytJA
France just put a digital tax on our great American technology companies. If anybody taxes them, it should be their… https://t.co/WIpeHmUp1A
Apple will not be given Tariff waiver, or relief, for Mac Pro parts that are made in China. Make them in the USA, no Tariffs!
Q2 GDP Up 2.1% Not bad considering we have the very heavy weight of the Federal Reserve anchor wrapped around our n… https://t.co/XhYbfHmFDb
There may or may not be National Security concerns with regard to Google and their relationship with China. If ther… https://t.co/7pwlRefEMF
....the fact that I have gone through a three year vicious Witch Hunt, perpetrated by the Lamestream Media in Collu… https://t.co/Jyn1QjlKpm
.@FoxNews is at it again. So different from what they used to be during the 2016 Primaries, &amp; before - Proud Warrio… https://t.co/0FKqhGXSoq
“Taken for Granted,” a wonderful new book by Gianno Caldwell on how Conservatism can win back the Americans that Li… https://t.co/hhiqMA0t0j
“Intelligence Community disappointed Mueller didn’t investigate the Steele Dossier.” @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews ...And plenty of other things!
I am pleased to announce the House has passed our budget deal 284-149. Great for our Military and our Vets. A big thank you!
Give A$AP Rocky his FREEDOM. We do so much for Sweden but it doesn’t seem to work the other way around. Sweden shou… https://t.co/imr6dTjmcX
Very disappointed in Prime Minister Stefan Löfven for being unable to act. Sweden has let our African American Comm… https://t.co/f0hfApJ8tz
...What took place was completely unacceptable, and will not be tolerated. Bill de Blasio should act immediately!
We love our Law Enforcement Officers all around this great Country. What took place in NYC with water being tossed… https://t.co/lhm9oB8BOs
Beautiful Welcome Ceremony at the Pentagon this morning for our new Secretary of Defense, Mark @EsperDoD! https://t.co/qYDkjmqnOd
House Republicans should support the TWO YEAR BUDGET AGREEMENT which greatly helps our Military and our Vets. I am totally with you!
Mark Levin on @foxandfriends now! Great guy.
Mark Levin will be on @foxandfriends now! Great guy.
President Trump’s Approval Rating on Economy is at 52%, a 4 point jump. Fox Poll @foxandfriends  Shouldn’t this be… https://t.co/bT71Cbcr9A
Fox Poll say best Economy in DECADES!
...impeachment, you have a Party of one. It’s over.” @kilmeade  “Nancy said, Jerry, please sit down. Very bad idea.… https://t.co/BrXGmizey7
“Yesterday changed everything, it really did clear the President. He wins.” @ainsleyearhardt  “It changed everythin… https://t.co/dwuRBYq5CJ
Appreciate it @LindseyGrahamSC, thank you! https://t.co/cGugEIXNOD
Thank you @MarkLevinShow! https://t.co/j4Y4kjrmdf
.@JaySekulow and @RudyGiuliani on @SeanHannity moments ago... https://t.co/Ecz4K3sOwh
"THE WITCH HUNT IS OVER!" @SeanHannity https://t.co/OUoIm4onJt
Great job @ChrisPlanteShow! https://t.co/ouTaP7WdFn
Thank you @TuckerCarlson @KimStrassel! https://t.co/kw9oGcRzrt
Thank you Rep. @DevinNunes! https://t.co/sifmkN7HDz
Thank you Rep. @Jim_Jordan! https://t.co/w9tF8xur44
Thank you @RepDougCollins! https://t.co/Lwc2ns2mQt
Thank you @GOPLeader McCarthy! https://t.co/0N4AeoRWK9
https://t.co/q5tjNpEzH0
“The Media’s Mueller Meltdown” @JesseBWatters https://t.co/EXdlk45ovU
The Democrats lost so BIG today. Their Party is in shambles right now...https://t.co/WDnGSOFzZU
The Democrats had nothing...
https://t.co/VUIMndS4lZ
https://t.co/yoWCQLM8Ad
“Impeachment’s over!”
@TerryMoran @ABCPolitics https://t.co/8J9ixCSnZC
Even Michael Moore agrees that the Dems and Mueller blew it! https://t.co/ZFPb50vi4v
“The kind of questions the White House Correspondents were asking is almost like they didn’t see what went on at th… https://t.co/AaLHAVkVYC
TRUTH IS A FORCE OF NATURE!
https://t.co/tNxUyfQIgD
https://t.co/wiOTBHQYt6
I would like to thank the Democrats for holding this morning’s hearing. Now, after 3 hours, Robert Mueller has to s… https://t.co/w2492yn1z9
“Mueller was asked whether or not the investigation was impeded in any way, and he said no.” In other words, there… https://t.co/fjsrc3iO7e
“This has been a disaster for the Democrats and a disaster for the reputation of Robert Mueller.” Chris Wallace @FoxNews
....interview, including the Vice President of the United States!
It has been reported that Robert Mueller is saying that he did not apply and interview for the job of FBI Director… https://t.co/5iv4SJ7OiX
KEEP AMERICA GREAT!
NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION!
So why didn’t the highly conflicted Robert Mueller investigate how and why Crooked Hillary Clinton deleted and acid… https://t.co/Nooz8I8RkD
Why didn’t Robert Mueller &amp; his band of 18 Angry Democrats spend any time investigating Crooked Hillary Clinton, Ly… https://t.co/ecLBnXESuS
It was NEVER agreed that Robert Mueller could use one of his many Democrat Never Trumper lawyers to sit next to him… https://t.co/MPN9h0UKl9
So Democrats and others can illegally fabricate a crime, try pinning it on a very innocent President, and when he f… https://t.co/JBHm7dk8Dv
So Robert Mueller has now asked for his long time Never Trumper lawyer to sit beside him and help with answers. Wha… https://t.co/UHs6iXFv6k
The young leaders here today (@TPUSA) are part of a movement unlike anything in the history of our nation. It is a… https://t.co/Jg68EYL8Om
Congratulations to our new Secretary of Defense, Mark @EsperDoD! https://t.co/aT3D1ZX5KK
Oh well, we still have the great @seanhannity who I hear has a really strong show tonight. 9:00 P.M.
THANK YOU @TPUSA! #MAGA https://t.co/1eqR2Im8dQ
Just watched Rep. Eric Swalwell be asked endless softball questions by @marthamaccallum on @FoxNews about the phony… https://t.co/wH56AcXWOv
Just got back only to hear of a last minute change allowing a Never Trumper attorney to help Robert Mueller with hi… https://t.co/qLlaTpFLPr
Budget Deal gives great victories to our Military and Vets, keeps out Democrat poison pill riders. Republicans and… https://t.co/TGY32x3VsN
....I got to know him over his many years as Chairman of the Police Athletic League, for which he devoted so much t… https://t.co/epNJchOdWY
I was saddened to learn of the recent passing of Bob Morgenthau, a truly great man! Bob served as a Naval Officer i… https://t.co/AuQiFW6RZD
Leaving for Turning Point USA. Will be speaking to some of the greatest and smartest young people on the planet. See you there!
When an old Wall at the Southern Border, that is crumbling and falling over, built in an important section to keep… https://t.co/DqCjkgEAyv
In 2016 I almost won Minnesota. In 2020, because of America hating anti-Semite Rep. Omar, &amp; the fact that Minnesota… https://t.co/AXWbivpGTo
....Tariffs, Remittance Fees, or all of the above. Guatemala has not been good. Big U.S. taxpayer dollars going to… https://t.co/2RGqQd9mSr
Guatemala, which has been forming Caravans and sending large numbers of people, some with criminal records, to the… https://t.co/bZp2YfXktE
Farmers are starting to do great again, after 15 years of a downward spiral. The 16 Billion Dollar China “replaceme… https://t.co/2tl4nu7Fmj
KEEP AMERICA GREAT!
Congratulations to Boris Johnson on becoming the new Prime Minister of the United Kingdom. He will be great!
....Best and Newest Military (almost totally rebuilt from the depleted military I took over) in History, Best V.A.… https://t.co/ARrR3hcXcy
Newest Poll: Only 11% in favor of starting ridiculous impeachment hearings. Well, let’s see: We have the Best Econo… https://t.co/TGyoyPIhiB
“I completely read the entire Mueller Report, and do you know what I concluded after reading both Volume 1 and Volu… https://t.co/7skzwM7P0e
https://t.co/GLiV8RGsNj
When we rip down and totally replace a badly broken and dilapidated Barrier on the Southern Border, something which… https://t.co/BRquugcPCQ
....This was a real compromise in order to give another big victory to our Great Military and Vets!
I am pleased to announce that a deal has been struck with Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, Senate Minority L… https://t.co/hYFLp1Wb8s
The “Squad” is a very Racist group of troublemakers who are young, inexperienced, and not very smart. They are pull… https://t.co/W2uNC05KOs
Going with First Lady to pay our respects to Justice Stevens. Leaving now!
The Report of Iran capturing CIA spies is totally false. Zero truth. Just more lies and propaganda (like their shot… https://t.co/6GD19cmzCe
....But the questions should be asked, why were all of Clinton’s people given immunity, and why were the text messa… https://t.co/cQ522ZYtd8
Highly conflicted Robert Mueller should not be given another bite at the apple. In the end it will be bad for him a… https://t.co/UVKsmG6vLG
Fake News Equals the Enemy of the People!
The Mainstream Media is out of control. They constantly lie and cheat in order to get their Radical Left Democrat v… https://t.co/H8r4mRUnst
....except for those stated by me, &amp; “reams of paper” were never given to me. It is a made up story meant to demean… https://t.co/RVIkDw5BLj
The Amazon Washington Post front page story yesterday was total Fake News. They said “Advisors wrote new talking po… https://t.co/u143RpgGUs
It is far more costly for the Federal Reserve to cut deeper if the economy actually does, in the future, turn down!… https://t.co/SSp8SBXNeW
....as we have done, it could have been soooo much better. Interest rate costs should have been much lower, &amp; GDP &amp;… https://t.co/1uQLACvA8A
With almost no inflation, our Country is needlessly being forced to pay a MUCH higher interest rate than other coun… https://t.co/j4zVcuQBVX
https://t.co/1DVvqFQxRK
Thank you very much for revealing the incredible facts, which the Fake News Media will never do! @SteveHiltonx… https://t.co/9EFtaomfKh
https://t.co/2lPjfxOKq3
....Based on the comments made by Senator Schumer, he must have seen how dangerous &amp; bad for our Country the Border… https://t.co/rpyZCeqxLI
Senator Chuck Schumer has finally gone to the Southern Border with some Democrat Senators. This is a GREAT thing! N… https://t.co/lae9K2Ldcf
....Most importantly you have led Israel with a commitment to the values of democracy, freedom, and equal opportuni… https://t.co/RYyS1fHnIo
Congratulations to Bibi @Netanyahu on becoming the longest serving PM in the history of Israel. Under your leadersh… https://t.co/DHOUaqHRZW
I don’t believe the four Congresswomen are capable of loving our Country. They should apologize to America (and Isr… https://t.co/EFUvL4LQOa
MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
Presidential Harassment!
The Washington Post Story, about my speech in North Carolina and tweet, with its phony sources who do not exist, is… https://t.co/CLLclXuxDN
Big progress at the Border, but Dems in Congress must change the Immigration Laws for all to be good! End the Loopholes and much more.
The Great State of West Virginia is producing record setting numbers and doing really well. When I became President… https://t.co/PPAbojuStO
I will help Angel Mom (and great woman) Mary Ann Mendoza with Twitter. I know Mary Ann from the beginning, and she… https://t.co/qJgZrQl7fD
Economic numbers reach an all time high, the best in our Country’s history. Great to be a part of something so good for so many!
https://t.co/aG45A3Ugnp
....Our teams will be talking further, and we agreed to speak again in the next 48 hours!
Just had a very good call with @SwedishPM Stefan Löfven who assured me that American citizen A$AP Rocky will be tre… https://t.co/9YiyUPTj1I
You can add 10% or 15% to this number. Economy doing better than EVER before! https://t.co/o59vI5tzXn
Thank you Bill. Very nice! https://t.co/hTnGiOh6T1
As you can see, I did nothing to lead people on, nor was I particularly happy with their chant. Just a very big and… https://t.co/A8wXOVSvsx
With the incompetent Mayor of London, you will never have safe streets! https://t.co/pJqL1NjyvA
Just spoke to @KanyeWest about his friend A$AP Rocky’s incarceration. I will be calling the very talented Prime Min… https://t.co/NbKHYs2QUX
Thank you! #MAGA2020 https://t.co/6G2TinCpWT
....Fed: There is almost no inflation!
....but it is no thanks to the Federal Reserve. Had they not acted so fast and “so much,” we would be doing even be… https://t.co/H5tdA4fJxi
I like New York Fed President John Williams first statement much better than his second. His first statement is 100… https://t.co/zR7KIy2Z6r
Because of the faulty thought process we have going for us at the Federal Reserve, we pay much higher interest rate… https://t.co/vufptVrS14
....Governor of the State did a good  job. That may be true but she could not have done it without the tremendous e… https://t.co/o18MOvBQ00
....he could not have been nicer or more respectful to your favorite President, me. Then I saw the column he wrote,… https://t.co/wpd3eWeFpn
Thomas “the Chin” Friedman, a weak and pathetic sort of guy, writes columns for The New York Times in between round… https://t.co/DVIv3LAFwF
....State which I will win in #2020 because they can’t stand her and her hatred of our Country, and they appreciate… https://t.co/2WkVWfvWZl
....Mainstream Media, which has lost all credibility, has either officially or unofficially become a part of the Ra… https://t.co/LWoKc2NRXX
It is amazing how the Fake News Media became “crazed” over the chant “send her back” by a packed Arena (a record) c… https://t.co/iBaECLN3hS
Great new book, “Justice On Trial, The Kavanaugh Confirmation and the Future of the Supreme Court.” Fantastic job b… https://t.co/DBGvN5zOYz
https://t.co/D7H1Wr1LHy
....working with labor and everyone else. He will be a great member of an Administration that has done more in the… https://t.co/wmPY2Cm1If
I am pleased to announce that it is my intention to nominate Gene Scalia as the new Secretary of Labor. Gene has le… https://t.co/iYXF7BTm8Y
Today, @FLOTUS Melania and I were honored to welcome members of Team USA to the @WhiteHouse for a great celebration… https://t.co/O9wwZrP8a8
This should have been taken care of years ago, the Trump Administration is taking care of these thugs now!
https://t.co/ulqagIAtxI
Today, on behalf of the American people, I received an American flag that flew aboard a ship carrying the first wav… https://t.co/bZ5ghgOxmF
I want to apprise everyone of an incident in the Strait of Hormuz today, involving #USSBoxer, a U.S. Navy amphibiou… https://t.co/P49VERsayu
....of gang members, in particular MS-13. ICE and Border Patrol are doing a great job!
Most of the MS-13 Gang members indicted &amp; arrested in L.A. were illegal aliens, 19 of 22. They are said to have kil… https://t.co/63725T5kY4
....of which was squandered away or wasted, never to be seen again. This is more than twice the amount given to Tex… https://t.co/yKeZ0y58Nh
A lot of bad things are happening in Puerto Rico. The Governor is under siege, the Mayor of San Juan is a despicabl… https://t.co/DtdQFiNoZx
Just returned to the White House from the Great State of North Carolina. What a crowd, and what great people. The e… https://t.co/1JBzcvWiLe
The Republican Party is the Party for ALL Americans. We are the Party of the American Worker, the American Family &amp;… https://t.co/Pb8QmQOqMn
Together, we will continue unleashing the power of American enterprise, so every American can know the dignity of w… https://t.co/Lm28Ljwh5i
THANK YOU Greenville, North Carolina! #MAGA2020 https://t.co/3ou3JzHsQX
....Greatest Economic BOOM in the history of our Country, the best job numbers, biggest tax reduction, rebuilt mili… https://t.co/3lMTVJvlBe
The United States House of Representatives has just overwhelmingly voted to kill the Resolution on Impeachment, 332… https://t.co/2rhYOwYzp4
See you tonight, North Carolina! #MAGA2020 https://t.co/rqOwEkTtqQ
GOD BLESS THE USA🇺🇸 https://t.co/w6FenobnlR
New Poll: The Rasmussen Poll, one of the most accurate in predicting the 2016 Election, has just announced that “Tr… https://t.co/e3gEj3Su0h
After a ten year search, the so-called “mastermind” of the Mumbai Terror attacks has been arrested in Pakistan. Gre… https://t.co/XoxP9gak3j
Big Rally tonight in Greenville, North Carolina. Lots of great things to tell you about, including the fact that ou… https://t.co/UWb4OOo6Dx
The Democrats in Congress are getting nothing done, not on drug pricing, not on immigration, not on infrastructure,… https://t.co/Up7YILcEvq
....they are destroying the Democrat Party. I’m appalled that so many of our Presidential candidates are falling al… https://t.co/q6TFFoInIs
...opinion, they’re Americans. Now I’m entitled to my opinion, &amp; I just think they’re left wing cranks. They’re the… https://t.co/LvUu2IXZO7
“In America, if you hate our Country, you are free to leave. The simple fact of the matter is, the four Congresswom… https://t.co/LCXtLlpsvn
....visible members of the House Democrats, who are now wedded to this bitterness and hate. The Republican vote was… https://t.co/XvLZidUI7r
So great to see how unified the Republican Party was on today’s vote concerning statements I made about four Democr… https://t.co/PxFy8wPIGG
Yesterday, it was my great honor to host our third annual Made in America Showcase at the @WhiteHouse.... https://t.co/mBha7Qprr9
Looking forward to tomorrow night’s rally in Greenville, North Carolina at 7:00 P.M. Eastern! https://t.co/oXRgDvjacc
Kevin McCarthy @GOPLeader, “The President’s Tweets were not Racist. The controversy over the tweets is ALL POLITICS… https://t.co/FLZRSiUqNc
.....Congresswomen, who I truly believe, based on their actions, hate our Country. Get a list of the HORRIBLE thing… https://t.co/mnDj43eq1k
Those Tweets were NOT Racist. I don’t have a Racist bone in my body! The so-called vote to be taken is a Democrat c… https://t.co/jAGPz1saBI
Our Country is Free, Beautiful and Very Successful. If you hate our Country, or if you are not happy here, you can leave!
If you come after the President, the Country, the Flag - he’s going to defend himself. What the squad doesn’t like… https://t.co/Zq8pGewq31
“Billionaire Tech Investor Peter Thiel believes Google should be investigated for treason. He accuses Google of wor… https://t.co/OXOb83lfoB
.....shouting of the F...word, among many other terrible things, and the petrified Dems run for the hills. Why isn’… https://t.co/RuKd0QnLOL
The Democrat Congresswomen have been spewing some of the most vile, hateful, and disgusting things ever said by a p… https://t.co/D5wtHor4lB
“The best economy in our lifetime!” @IngrahamAngle
MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
The Obama Administration built the Cages, not the Trump Administration! DEMOCRATS MUST GIVE US THE VOTES TO CHANGE BAD IMMIGRATION LAWS.
The Dems were trying to distance themselves from the four “progressives,” but now they are forced to embrace them.… https://t.co/5LO2uugHp0
....Detention facilities are not Concentration Camps! America has never been stronger than it is now – rebuilt Mili… https://t.co/WlTKWSaqNP
....They are anti-Israel, pro Al-Qaeda, and comment on the 9/11 attack, “some people did something.” Radical Left D… https://t.co/82AZtIEzwx
We will never be a Socialist or Communist Country. IF YOU ARE NOT HAPPY HERE, YOU CAN LEAVE! It is your choice, and… https://t.co/ShbHZSmpLw
Here we go with the Fake Polls. Just like what happened with the Election against Crooked Hillary Clinton. ABC, NBC… https://t.co/F4Zf2gEI8E
.....to impeach President Trump on DAY ONE. Make them the face of the future of the Democrat Party, you will destro… https://t.co/BwgUnFcK2w
....What does it mean for America to have free Healthcare for Illegal Immigrants, no criminalization of coming into… https://t.co/iaPyyxxh8U
....they are Anti-Semitic, they are Anti-America, we don’t need to know anything about them personally, talk about… https://t.co/J6TJAe62ql
“We all know that AOC and this crowd are a bunch of Communists, they hate Israel, they hate our own Country, they’r… https://t.co/Htq3Dsm5TZ
If Democrats want to unite around the foul language &amp; racist hatred spewed from the mouths and actions of these ver… https://t.co/GAtawnjE9d
When will the Radical Left Congresswomen apologize to our Country, the people of Israel and even to the Office of t… https://t.co/xCPlEhKpLj
....with the U.S., and wishes it had not broken the original deal in the first place. In the meantime, we are recei… https://t.co/iBHxQvWJAu
China’s 2nd Quarter growth is the slowest it has been in more than 27 years. The United States Tariffs are having a… https://t.co/tJ6p3s3zF3
We are doing great Economically as a Country, Number One, despite the Fed’s antiquated policy on rates and tightening. Much room to grow!
....and the many terrible things they say about the United States must not be allowed to go unchallenged. If the De… https://t.co/PqNIlCqCbk
So sad to see the Democrats sticking up for people who speak so badly of our Country and who, in addition, hate Isr… https://t.co/cBsB3XZcUf
Think what it would be without the 3 year Witch Hunt and Fake News Media, in partnership with the Democrats! https://t.co/KBtl7wde0F
https://t.co/YaiCXrxYQq
.....Sorry, can’t let them into our Country. If too crowded, tell them not to come to USA, and tell the Dems to fix… https://t.co/mSz4IgKAJA
Friday’s tour showed vividly, to politicians and the media, how well run and clean the children’s detention centers… https://t.co/wS6i8qileI
Thank you, so nice, but we are getting it done anyway! https://t.co/w2fhJK6FmF
....it is done. These places need your help badly, you can’t leave fast enough. I’m sure that Nancy Pelosi would be… https://t.co/8IoVStRDut
....and viciously telling the people of the United States, the greatest and most powerful Nation on earth, how our… https://t.co/xPRSZHNNAd
So interesting to see “Progressive” Democrat Congresswomen, who originally came from countries whose governments ar… https://t.co/W7GAYLJ5Ki
A big risk of major flooding in large parts of Louisiana and all across the Gulf Coast. Please be very careful!
94% Approval Rating in the Republican Party, an all time high. Ronald Reagan was 87%. Thank you!
....Paul Ryan almost killed the Republican Party. Weak, ineffective &amp; stupid are not exactly the qualities that Rep… https://t.co/hjU8enIj4h
House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy is a far superior leader than was Lame Duck Speaker Paul Ryan. Tougher, smarte… https://t.co/4j8rVuEGcq
This is one of the most horrible abuses of all. Those texts between gaga lovers would have told the whole story. Il… https://t.co/HDIw6kmC1w
Andy McCabe is a major sleazebag. Among many other things, he took massive amounts of money from Crooked Hillary re… https://t.co/Hd6UKQ8qGr
“MUELLER’S PARTISAN WITCH HUNT!” https://t.co/XTD5f5ZOz2
"EXPOSING THE REAL 2016 ELECTION SCANDAL!" https://t.co/WUNOSKZC6T
"BOOMERANG OF JUSTICE" @SeanHannity https://t.co/MUbkCXRpfM
Just returned to the beautiful @WhiteHouse after a great day in Wisconsin and Ohio! https://t.co/WVp3KeKg8h
Leaving the Great State of Ohio! https://t.co/WTLC1fFzWl
The DOW, S&amp;P 500, and NASDAQ all close the week at a new record high! https://t.co/wPJiM8n7m2
Tennessee loving Bill Hagerty, who was my Tennessee Victoy Chair and is now the very outstanding Ambassador to Japa… https://t.co/5x1dVlydPn
I am thrilled to be back in the Great State of Wisconsin with the extraordinary men &amp; women of Derco Aerospace! We… https://t.co/aysfODs1N5
We have a GREAT TEAM in Pennsylvania! I’m proud to say that our good friends Lawrence Tabas &amp; Bernadette “Bernie” C… https://t.co/FcgY2aQT9Q
....Alex was a great Secretary of Labor and his service is truly appreciated. He will be replaced on an acting basi… https://t.co/eGlhTXzfEz
Alex Acosta informed me this morning that he felt the constant drumbeat of press about a prosecution which took pla… https://t.co/UktqH53cgj
Wow, @CNN RATINGS HAVE CRASHED. LOST ALL CREDIBILITY!
Great job by Rush Limbaugh on @foxandfriends!
.....if Mexico produces (which I think they will). Biggest part of deal with Mexico has not yet been revealed! Chin… https://t.co/nngTOXUD7r
....companies to come to the USA and to get companies that have left us for other lands to COME BACK HOME. We  stup… https://t.co/AwhJKSZa0v
When you are the big “piggy bank” that other countries have been ripping off for years (to a level that is not to b… https://t.co/YttIDsCfft
@SebGorka Wins Big, No Contest!
The Great Rush Limbaugh will be on @foxandfriends at 8:30 A.M. Enjoy!
